gigenet.com 2013-12-27

# Information We Collect and How We Use It | GigeNET' Privacy Policy

### **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the ‘Do we use cookies?’ section below for information about cookies and how we use them. 

### **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions (Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or  
given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails (The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news,updates, related product or service information, etc.) 
  * To effectively use remarketing ads displayed through third-party vendors such as Google. (Third-party vendors such as Google use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s previous visits to our website. To opt out of Google’s use of cookies for remarketing purposes you can visit Google’s [Ads Preference Manager](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). Alternatively, to opt out of the use of other third-party vendor’s use of cookies visit the [Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out Page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). To opt out of Teracent Cookie usage for Dynamic Ad Service please visit the [Teracent Opt-Out Page](http://www.teracent.com/about-us/opt-out).)

**Note:** If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

### **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required  
to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will be kept on file for more than 60 days in order to process your monthly recurring hosting service invoices, along with any other incidental charges such as bandwidth overage fees.

### **Do we use cookies?**

Yes, cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you choose to allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. Thessupport@gigenet.come service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you  
can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.

### **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and  
independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.

### **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any  
information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### **Terms and Conditions**

support@gigenet.comsupport@gigenet.comsupport@gigenet.com

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website [here.](http://www.gigenet.com/terms-of-service)

### **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy and the terms dictated with in.

### **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 4 July, 2013. 

### **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

545 E. Algonquin Rd. Ste. D  
Arlington Heights, IL 60005  
USA  
800-561-2656
